[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chemiluminescence is a phenomenon involving which of the following processes?", "correct_answer": "Emitting light", "incorrect_answers": ["Reflecting light", "Refracting light", "Transmitting light"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what substance is vitamin K soluble?", "correct_answer": "Fat", "incorrect_answers": ["Water", "All of these", "Protein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This chemical element is the final element produced by stellar nucleosynthesis and the heaviest element which does not require a supernova for its formation.", "correct_answer": "Iron", "incorrect_answers": ["Lead", "Carbon", "Oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What distinction does Dennis Tito hold?", "correct_answer": "He was the first tourist in space.", "incorrect_answers": ["He was the first person to fly the Shuttle, shoot down an enemy  fighter, and fly a balloon across the Atlantic.", "He was the first person to fly the Shuttle three times.", "He was the first person to make a space walk."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these statements about the Seismosaurus, the Earth-shaking lizard, is wrong?", "correct_answer": "Its hind legs were shorter than its front legs.", "incorrect_answers": ["It could reach 33 meters in length.", "It was recognized as a species in 1991.", "It was herbivorous."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When a panda is born, it is impossible to tell if it is male or female. How old is the panda before its gender is known?", "correct_answer": "4 years", "incorrect_answers": ["3 months", "1 year", "6 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "High surface tension, one of waters properties, is crucial for the survival of life on the planet, because it enables what vital process?", "correct_answer": "Transport of nutrients", "incorrect_answers": ["Dissolving of nutrients", "Recycling of nutrients", "Formation of nutrients"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What correctly describes the character of Chieko in the 2006 movie Babel?", "correct_answer": "She is deaf and mute.", "incorrect_answers": ["She is a musical prodigy.", "She is the typical Tokyo teenager.", "She is blind."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was nationality of Vladimir Remek - the first cosmonaut from a country other than the Soviet Union or the United States?", "correct_answer": "Czechoslovak", "incorrect_answers": ["Hungarian", "Bulgarian", "Pole"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before the F/A18 this was the main U.S. Marine Corps fighter/bomber.", "correct_answer": "Harrier", "incorrect_answers": ["Cobra", "Thunderbolt", "Tiger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word does Willy Wonka find difficult to pronounce and starts stuttering every time he tries to utter it in the 2005 movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory?", "correct_answer": "Parents", "incorrect_answers": ["Diet", "Gum", "Human"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This asteroid, orbiting around the sun, is sometimes called the second moon of the Earth but it is not a real satellite.", "correct_answer": "Cruithne", "incorrect_answers": ["Vesta", "Pallas", "Davida"]}]